Henry Snopek

Web Developer and Software Engineer 13455 W Fountain Dr. Apt 201 New Berlin, WI 53151 (262) 923-0261, hhsnopek@gmail.com, https://hhsnopek.com

About

I'm an experienced Full Stack Developer interested in pushing the boundaries of the web. Working at an agency since 2015 I've been fortunate to work on an extremely wide range of projects, gaining experience in both backend and frontend technologies, and also experimenting with the latest tools and technologies. I've worked on various projects with small and large teams, including other departments. I actively participate in open source software, whether it's helping another developer, writing documentation, or bug fixing I strive to commit daily. I'm particularly interested in Electron applications, Progress Web Apps, and Static websites.

Education

Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science, Carroll University, Waukesha, WI May 2016

<u>Skills</u>

Languages: Javascript, Golang, Bash Source Code Management: Git

Frameworks/Technologies: React, Electron & Node, GraphQL, RESTful APIs, Webpack, Parcel Bundler, Nginx,

AWS management & deployment, Docker, Headless CMS, Linux

Experience

Developer, Carrot Creative (rebranded to Virtue), Brooklyn, NYC

June 2016 – Present

- Assisted in product development of suave.com rebuild with Adobe Experience Manager
- Managed and developed frontend tooling for static sites with Roots, Spike, and React Static
- Built Single Page Applications using Create React App (pinterestsecretsanta.com)
- Lead developer and client contact for P&G Children's Safe Drinking Water rebuild of csdw.org
- Mentored coworkers on various tooling (create-react-app, spike, & react-static), react, golang APIs, and in both frontend & backend best-practices

Developer Intern, Carrot Creative, Brooklyn, NYC

June 2015 – Aug 2015

- Refactored Share Button, +3000 stars, +65 million asset requests/month (github.com/carrot/share-button)
- Proposed and rewrote Carrot internal apps using Microservices with Golang and Docker
- Led development of tumblr themes for Espolon Tequila (psstzine.tumblr.com) and Elizabeth Arden (teamtaylorswiftfragrances.tumblr.com)

Open Source Projects & Contributions

Beer O'Clock (github.com/hhsnopek/beeroclock)

Jan 2017

Proof of concept Bash service

Blog Writeup (hackernoon.com/a-web-service-written-in-pure-bash-2af847902df1)

Up (github.com/apex/up)

Nov 2017 - Present

Deploy infinitely scalable serverless apps, apis, and sites in seconds to AWS.

Code Frame (github.com/hhsnopek/code-frame)

Aug 2016 - Present

Minimal Code Frame like babel-code-frame, but smaller

Jumblr (github.com/hhsnopek/jumblr)

Oct 2014 - May 2015

Jade Tumblr Mixins

10Kft Stopwatch (github.com/carrot/10k-stopwatch)

July 2014

A chrome extension that starts/stops the time tracker that hooks into 10000ft.com

roots (roots.cx)
A toolbox for building simple, beautiful, and efficient products for the web.

ship (github.com/carrot/ship)

Dec 2013 - 2016

May 2013 - 2016

Multi-platform deployment with node.